acephotos.org 2018-06-01

# Privacy Policy

## 1\. General

Lucy Media welcomes you. This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and interactive services owned or operated by Lucy Media and its subsidiaries which include, but are not limited to, FamousFix.com, WhosDatedWho.com, FanPix.net, AllStarPics.net, LucyWho.com, LucyLooks.com, LucyMe.com, BDBPhotos.com, LucyPhotos.com and TheBaseballWebsite.com (individually the "Service"; together the "Services").

Lucy Media is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit or use the Services as further outlined in this policy. As a condition of using the Services, you agree to provide Lucy Media with certain personal information. This information includes, but not limited to: your email address as well as your demographic information (e.g., hometown, gender, and age). Please note that nowhere on the Services do we knowingly collect contact information from children under the age of 14. Please review this privacy policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. Each time you visit or use the Services, or provide us with information, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time. You agree that by using the Services you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails, as described below in this privacy policy.

## 2\. Changes to Privacy Policy

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Services or as we incorporate suggestions from our users. If we are going to use or disclose your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time we collected the information, you will have a choice as to whether or not we use or disclose your information in this new manner. We will also post a notification that the Privacy Policy has been amended prominently on the Services so that you can always review what information we gather, how we might use that information, and under which conditions we will disclose it to anyone.

## 3\. How Your Information is Used

### Contacting You for Offers and Promotions:

You agree, in consideration for the use of the Services provided by Lucy Media, to allow Lucy Media to use your personal information to send you marketing and promotional materials. Lucy Media may also send you marketing and promotional materials that promote third party products. Lucy Media will not rent or sell your personal information for use by third parties. These materials may include, but are not limited to: newsletters providing you with additional information on how to use the Services, and promotional offers for goods and services from Lucy Media or third parties.

### Use of Demographic Information:

Lucy Media may use your demographic information to perform business analyses or to tailor the Services and communications to your interests. We may share anonymous, aggregated demographic information with advertisers and other third parties so that they can tailor their advertisements and communications to the appropriate audience. Any time that we are allowed under this privacy policy to share your contact information, we may also share your demographic information along with it.

## 4\. Disclosure to Governmental Entities

Lucy Media may disclose specific contact information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with law, to cooperate with or seek assistance from law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of Lucy Media or other visitors or users of the Services. Also, your contact information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a merger, acquisition, consolidation, divestiture, or a bankruptcy of Lucy Media.

## 5\. Use of Cookies and Other Site Tracking Data

### Cookies:

A "cookie" is a small file that we save on your computer's hard drive that contains non-personal information. These cookies help to give you faster access to pages you have already visited. They also allow you to personalize your pages, and optimize your experience at our sites. We also use cookies to help us figure out how many people visit our sites, which of our web pages they visit, and how long they stay there. This information helps us figure out which of our web features are highly successful and which sites might need improvement. You can disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but allow you to disable them. Disabling cookies may prevent you from properly using or accessing the Services.

### Session IDs:

"Session IDs" allow us to identify a particular user across multiple web page requests. This Session ID is maintained within your cookie file, where possible. If cookies are not enabled, or if The user's internet browser program does not support cookies then Lucy Media will place the Session ID in the requested web page. This allows the end user to avoid having to continually re-enter Certain information such as account name and password for every web page request. This Session ID expires whenever the user closes their internet browser.

### Web Site Tracking, Reporting:

Many of our web pages also contain special electronic images (called a "single-pixel gif" or "gifs") that allow us to gather only non-personally identifiable traffic statistics and other aggregate information about visitors to our sites. Lucy Media (through itself or third parties) uses this technology to collect and accumulate anonymous data that helps us understand and analyze the experience of people visiting the Services and, along with other information you provide, customize your future visits and improve the Services. For example, we capture data on the type of browser used, operating system software (e.g. Windows 95 vs. 98 or Macintosh), cookie preferences (whether the user has them turned on or off), and search engine keywords (what key words did a visitor use to get to the Services). We also record number of visits, paths taken, and time spent on sites and pages within the Services. Please keep in mind that none of this information is personally identifiable and that we only distribute this information to internal staff at Lucy Media

### Banner Ads:

The Services may include the use of ad banner partners for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions, and other marketing messages. These ads may be provided, in some cases, by a third party ad service provider. The ad service provider may place or utilize their own unique cookie on your browser, and may use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our sites, such as the number of times you have viewed the ad. Lucy Media is not responsible for the collection of these cookies and is not responsible for the actions of the ad service providers. Lucy Media does not sponsor, endorse or guarantee any products or services advertised by third parties on the Services.

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here:

<http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>

### Direct Linking URLs or Hotlinking:

In order to provide more relevant advertising and monitor user bandwidth usage (as governed by the Lucy Media Terms of Service), Lucy Media may gather data from the referer logs that identify where and how frequently user images being hosted by Lucy Media are being displayed on third party sites.

## 6\. Information from Other Sites

Lucy Media may place links to other web sites operated by other parties and from time to time may include information and links to third party web sites in our promotional email. Some of these other web sites contain our brand names and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on these links and visit these other web sites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control these other web sites or these other web sites' business practices, and that this privacy policy does not apply to these other web sites. Consequently, the operators of these other web sites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on the Services. We encourage you to review their privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions.

## 7\. Non-US Users

If you are not a resident of the United States, you understand and agree that Lucy Media stores and processes your information on computers located in the United States, and by providing any data to Lucy Media, you consent to the transfer of such information to the United States.

## 8\. Security Precautions

Lucy Media has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Your information may be transferred to and maintained in whole or in part on computer networks which may be located outside of the state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction in which you reside, and may be stored on equipment or in facilities leased or licensed from third parties. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information and make all commercially reasonable efforts to do so, Lucy Media cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. However, once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. This privacy policy does not apply to any information, including such photographs, that you submit for use in publicly available areas. We ask that you do not submit any personal information, including contact information or financial information, for display in public areas, as other people who use the Services will see it. If you submit such information for display in public areas, Lucy Media cannot prevent it from being used in a manner that violates the law, your personal privacy or your safety. By submitting such information for display in public areas, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed.

**ADDITIONAL PROVISIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY THAT ARE APPLICABLE TO EEA RESIDENTS**

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our websites in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via privacy AT exponential DOT com

In addition to Exponential, the following partners also have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising, audience and ad measurement. Please contact the partners directly using the privacy policy links below for opt-out requests, access requests or complaints:

Content.ad: [Privacy Policy](https://www.content.ad/privacy-policy/)

Facebook: [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

Google: [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

Brealtime: [Privacy Policy](http://www.brealtime.com/privacy-policy/)

Quantcast: [Privacy Policy](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/)

Apart from the data collected and stored by our partners, Lucy Media does not collect any additional information about the people using our websites. Lucy Media is solely interested in building a publicly-available information resource for fans.
